Guide to the UE News Photograph Collection, 1933-1998 UE.14.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Individuals and Topics, 14.1.4.
  - Mingo, Frank: Local 101 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Mintz, Robert: Organizer (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Mitchell, Wesley: Local 441 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Mitton, Joseph: Local 103 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Mooney, Jerold: Local 501 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Mroz, Steven: Local 1114 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Mueluer, Emil: Local 1113 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Mugford, Walter: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - "Muggy" (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Murphy, Mary (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Neal, Sterling: District 7 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Neill, Thomas (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Nelson, Harry (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Nelson, John: Local 506 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Neputy, Peter: Local 101 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Newcombe, James: Local 401 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Newell, Amy R. (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Newell, Charles: International Representative (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Niebur, Richard: District 7 President (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Nixon, Russ: Washington Representative (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Norwood, Isaiah: Local 1421 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Oakes, Grant: District 11 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - O'Connor, Harvey (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Onofaro, Nicholas (See also District 1) (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Ordower, Sidney: District 11 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Orfinik, Michael: Local 450 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Overby, Elizabeth Moore: Local 747 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Painter, Dennis (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - Panzino, Frank (See also District 6) (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Pare, Jean: District 5 (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Payne, James: Local 813 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Perry, Douglas: District 2 President (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Peterson, Andrew: Local 301 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Phelps, Harry (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Pogue, Joseph: District 8 President (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Poineau, Roderique (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Polaski, Sandi: Westinghouse International Representative (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Polich, Vance: Local 157 FE (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Price, James: Local 107 (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Quinn, Thomas (see also Founding Officers) (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Quirini, Helen: Local 301 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Raley, Talmadge: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Ratner, David: UE Comptroller (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - Reed, Marie: Local 735 (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Reisel, Victor (Box 25, Folder 98)
  - Repaal, W.E.: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 99)
  - Rice, Robert: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Riskin, Benjamin (Box 25, Folder 101)
  - Rivers, Charles (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Robinson, Cleveland: District 65 Secretary Treasurer (Box 25, Folder 103)
  - Rooney, George: Local 450 (Box 25, Folder 104)
  - Rosen, Frank: District 11 President (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - Salter, Herbert: Local 259 (Box 25, Folder 106)
  - Salveggio, Joseph (Box 25, Folder 107)
  - Sanchez, Rafael (Box 25, Folder 108)
  - Sangiovanni (Box 25, Folder 109)
  - Sardi, Louis: Local 404 (Box 25, Folder 110)
  - Sario, John (Box 25, Folder 111)
  - Sarti, Louis (Box 25, Folder 112)
  - Savitsky, Ed: Local 107 (Box 25, Folder 113)
  - Sayler, Frances: Wife of Organizer (Box 25, Folder 114)
  - Scherer, Marcel (Box 25, Folder 115)
  - Schlenker, Kathryn J. (Kitty): Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 116)
  - Schumann, Louis: Local 401 President (Box 25, Folder 117)
  - Schwab, Charles: Local 639 (Box 25, Folder 118)
  - Scribner, David: General Counsel (Box 25, Folder 119)
  - Sentner, Antonia (Box 25, Folder 120)
  - Sentner, William (Box 25, Folder 121)
  - Seymour, Paul: District 2 (Box 25, Folder 122)
  - Shaiken, Harley (Box 25, Folder 123)
  - Sharkey, Thomas: Local 107 President (Box 25, Folder 124)
  - Shattuck, Raymond: Local 431 (Box 25, Folder 125)
  - Simon, Hal: Local 1227 (Box 25, Folder 126)
  - Sims, Charles: Local 754 (Box 25, Folder 127)
  - Smith, Albert L. (Box 25, Folder 128)
  - Smith, Daniel: District 6 President (Box 25, Folder 129)
  - Smith, Elbert (Box 25, Folder 130)
  - Smith, Floyd: Local 315 (Box 25, Folder 131)
  - Smith, Philip (Box 25, Folder 132)
  - Smith, William D.: UE-FE 70 (Box 25, Folder 133)
  - Southern, Trudi: District 10 President (Box 25, Folder 134)
  - Spero, Nathan: UE Director of Research (Box 25, Folder 135)
  - Spinozzi, Constance: District 1 President (Box 25, Folder 136)
  - Squires, Joseph H.: Local 825 (Box 25, Folder 137)
  - Stackhouse, Frank M.: Local 1001 (Box 25, Folder 138)
  - Stager, Waldo: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 139)
  - Stamler, Rose: Local 1225 (Box 25, Folder 140)
  - Stanfield, Revel: Local 766 (Box 25, Folder 141)
  - Staniard, Geraldine (Box 25, Folder 142)
  - Stein, Thelma: District 4 (Box 25, Folder 143)
  - Steinberg, Jerry: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 144)
  - Steiner, Charles: Local 475 (Box 25, Folder 145)
  - Stevens, George: International Representative (Box 25, Folder 146)
  - Stone, Lulu: Local 475 (Box 25, Folder 147)
  - Stowe, Leland: UE Radio Commentator (Box 25, Folder 148)
  - Swan, Elvis: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 149)
  - Swanson, Samuel (Box 25, Folder 150)
  - Thompson, Ernest (Box 25, Folder 151)
  - Thornton, Peggy: Local 103 (Box 25, Folder 152)
  - Tice, Esther (Box 25, Folder 153)
  - Tomassetti, Nicholas J. (Box 25, Folder 154)
  - Tormey, Donald: International Representative (Box 25, Folder 155)
  - Torre, Louis (Box 25, Folder 156)
  - Turkowski, Joseph: International Representative and Vanclief, Jeep (Box 25, Folder 157)
  - Vandever, Lloyd: District 10 President (Box 25, Folder 158)
  - Vasi, James (Box 25, Folder 159)
  - Vejlupek, Joseph (Box 25, Folder 160)
  - Veneri, Marty: Local 426 (Box 25, Folder 161)
  - Villarreal, Gabriel: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 162)
  - Wallace, Clarence E. (Box 25, Folder 163)
  - Wallace, William: District 4 Secretary and Paid Informant (Box 25, Folder 164)
  - Washington, Ed (Box 25, Folder 165)
  - Ward, Robert: Local 522 (Box 25, Folder 166)
  - Ward, Harold (Box 25, Folder 167)
  - Waybur, Bruce (Box 25, Folder 168)
  - Weatherby, Glenice: Local 255 (Box 25, Folder 169)
  - Weber, Joseph: Director of Organization (Box 25, Folder 170)
  - Weinhermer, Frank: Local 430 (Box 25, Folder 171)
  - Weir, Mary: Local 119 (Box 25, Folder 172)
  - Weixel, Lola (Box 25, Folder 173)
  - White, Francis: Field Organizer (Box 25, Folder 174)
  - White, Marshall: Local 301 (Box 25, Folder 175)
  - White, Sara: Local 716 (Box 25, Folder 176)
  - Wiedorfer, Sgt. Paul (Box 25, Folder 177)
  - Willard, Josephine (Box 25, Folder 178)
  - Wishart, Robert: District 11 (Box 25, Folder 179)
  - Womack, Mel: International Representative (Box 25, Folder 180)
  - Wright, Fred: UE News Cartoonist (Box 25, Folder 181)
  - Wright, Theodore: Local 610 Organizer (Box 25, Folder 182)
  - Wright, Thomas (Box 25, Folder 183)
  - Young, Ruth (Box 25, Folder 184)
  - Zamosky, Stanley (Box 25, Folder 185)
  - Abzug, Bella S.: Representative D-NY (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Adair, E. Ross: Representative R-IN (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Adams, Brock: Representative D-WA (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Addabo, Joseph: Representative D-NY (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Aiken, George D: Senator R-VT (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Asner, Ed: President Screen Actors Guild (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Badillo, Herman: Representative D-NY (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Baldwin, C.B.: CIO-PAC (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Baldwin, Raymond: Senator R-CT (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Ball, Joseph: Senator R-MN (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Barden, Graham A.: Representative D-NC (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Barkley, Alben: Senator D-KY (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Barrett, William A.: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Bayh, Birch: Senator D-IN (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Beall, J. Glenn: Senator R-MD (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Bender, George H.: Senator R-OH (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Bergoff, Pearl: Bureau for Spies (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Bernard, John: Representative D-MN (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Biaggi, Mario: Representative R-NY (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Bingham, Dr. Eula: OSHA Administration (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Bland, Schuyler Otis: Representative D-VA (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Blatnik, John: Representative D-MN (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Bolton, Frances: Representative R-OH (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Bolton, Oliver P.: Representative R-OH (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Botha, Thozamile: SACTU (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Boulware, Lemuel: GE Chairman (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Boyle, Charles: Representative D-IL (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Bradley, Thomas: Mayor Los Angeles (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Bramblett, Ernest R.: Representative R-CA (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Bridges, Harry: ILWU President (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Brooke, Edward W.: Senator D-MA (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Brown, Elmer: International Typographical Union President (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Brownwell, Herbert: Attorney General (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Brutus, Dennis: Exiled South African Poet (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Buchanan, Frank: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Burdick, Usher L.: Representative R-ND (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Burton, Harold: Senator R-OH (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Burton, John: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Burton, Philip: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Bush, Prescott: Senator R-CT (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Butler, John M. Senator R-MD (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Byrne, James A.: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Byrnes, James F.: Secretary of State (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Bywater, William: IUE President (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Capehart, Homer: Senator R-IN (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Carlson, Frank: Senator R-KS (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Carter, Amy: Daughter of U.S. President (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Carter, Jimmy: U. S. President (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Cassidy, Martin: Radio and Television Workers (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Celler, Emanuel: Representative D-NY (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Chambers, William CIO-PAC (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Chavez, Cesar: Labor Actvist (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Chisholm, Shirley: Representative D-NY (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Christopher, George: Mayor San Francisco (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Church, Frank: Senator D-ID (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Clark, John: Mine-Mill (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Clark, Joseph: Senator D-PA (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Clay, William: Representative D-MO (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Cleveland, James C.: Representative R-NH (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Collier, Harold R.: Representative R-IL (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Collins, Cardiss: Representative D-IL (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Commoner, Barry: Professor (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Connolly, Thomas: Senator D-OH (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Conte, Silvio: Representative R-MA (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Conyers, John: Representative D-MI (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Copeland, Royal S.: Senator D-NY (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Corbett, Robert J.: Representative R-PA (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Cordiner, Ralph: GE President (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Counts, Curtis J.: Director Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Coyne, William: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Craypo, Charles: Professor Cornell University (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Cree, Albert E.: Representative of VT Governor (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Curtin, Willard S.: Representative R-PA (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - Curtis, Carl T.: Representative R-NE (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Daschle, Thomas: Senator D-SD (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Davenport, Harry S.: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Dellums, Ronald: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Dennison, David S. Jr.: Representative R-OH (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Dent, John H.: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Derwinski, Edward J.: Representative R-IL (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - D'Ewart, Wesley A.: Representative R-MT (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - Dies, Martin: Representative D-TX (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - Diggs, Charles C. Jr.: Representative D-MI (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - Diogvardi, John: Labor Racketeer (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - Dirksen, Everett: Senator R-IL (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - Dixon, Alan: Senator D-IL (Box 26, Folder 86)
  - Dlamini, Christopher: President Federation of South African Trade Unionists (Box 26, Folder 87)
  - Dodd, Thomas: Senator D-CT (Box 26, Folder 88)
  - Dondero, George A.: Representative R-MI (Box 26, Folder 89)
  - Donohue, Harold D.: Representative D-MA (Box 26, Folder 90)
  - Donovan, Raymond: Secretary of Labor (Reagan) (Box 26, Folder 91)
  - Douglas, Helen Gahagan: Performer: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 92)
  - Douglas, William O.: Justice Supreme Court (Box 26, Folder 93)
  - Drinan, Robert: Representative D-MA (Box 26, Folder 94)
  - Dubinsky, David: President International Ladies Garment Workers (Box 26, Folder 95)
  - DuBois, W.E.B.: Civil Rights Activist (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Duff, James H.: Senator R-PA (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Dukakis, Michael: Massachusetts Governor (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - Dulles, John Foster: Secretary of State (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - Eastland, James H.: Senator D-MS (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - Eberharter, Herman P.: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 101)
  - Edgar, Robert W.: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 102)
  - Edwards, Don: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 103)
  - Einstein, Albert: Scientist (Box 26, Folder 104)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David: U.S. President (Box 26, Folder 105)
  - Fallon, George H.: Representative D-MD (Box 26, Folder 106)
  - Fasanella, Ralph: Artist (Box 26, Folder 107)
  - Fauntroy, Walter: Representative D-DC (Box 26, Folder 108)
  - Fayette, Frederick J.: Senator D-VT (Box 26, Folder 109)
  - Feinglass, Abe: Vice President Meatcutters Union (Box 26, Folder 110)
  - Feingold, Russ: Senator D-WI (Box 26, Folder 111)
  - Ferguson, Homer: Senator R- MI (Box 26, Folder 112)
  - Finley, Murray: ACWA (Box 26, Folder 113)
  - Fitzmaurice, David: IUE President (Box 26, Folder 114)
  - Fitzsimmons, Frank E.: President Teamsters Union (Box 26, Folder 115)
  - Flanders, Ralph E.: Senator R-VT (Box 26, Folder 116)
  - Flemming, W. Robert: Representative D-IN (Box 26, Folder 117)
  - Flood, Daniel J.: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 118)
  - Foner, Philip: Labor Historian (Box 26, Folder 119)
  - Forand, Aime: Representative D-RI (Box 26, Folder 120)
  - Fowler, Harper: Professor: U.S. Dept of Interior (Box 26, Folder 121)
  - Frankensteen, Richard: UAW (Box 26, Folder 122)
  - Fraser, Donald M.: Representative D-MN (Box 26, Folder 123)
  - Freeman, Gordon: IBEW President (Box 26, Folder 124)
  - Friedel, Samuel N.: Representative D-MD (Box 26, Folder 125)
  - Fulbright, J. William: Senator D-AR (Box 26, Folder 126)
  - Fulton, James G.: Representative R-PA (Box 26, Folder 127)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth: Professor (Box 26, Folder 128)
  - Garmatz, Edward A.: Representative D-MD (Box 26, Folder 129)
  - Gellert, Hugo: Artist (Box 26, Folder 130)
  - Giaimo, Robert N.: Representative D-CT (Box 26, Folder 131)
  - Gillie, George W.: Representative R-IN (Box 26, Folder 132)
  - Goldwater, Barry: Senator R-AZ (Box 26, Folder 133)
  - Gorman, Patrick: Meatcutters Secretary Treasurer (Box 26, Folder 134)
  - Grabowski, Bernard F.: Representative D-CT (Box 26, Folder 135)
  - Gravel, Michael: Senator D-AK (Box 26, Folder 136)
  - Green, John: Marine and Ship Building Workers (Box 26, Folder 137)
  - Green, William J.: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 138)
  - Gregory, Richard: Performer (Box 26, Folder 139)
  - Griebel, Richard H.: President Fairbanks, Morse and Company (Box 26, Folder 140)
  - Griswold, Dwight: Senator R-NE (Box 26, Folder 141)
  - Gruening, Ernest: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 142)
  - Guinier, Ewart: Professor (Box 26, Folder 143)
  - Hagan, Harlen: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 144)
  - Hallinan, Vincent with Charlotta Bass "Prominent American" (Box 26, Folder 145)
  - Harrington, Michael J.: Representative D-MA (Box 26, Folder 146)
  - Hartke, Vance: Senator D-IN (Box 26, Folder 147)
  - Hartley, F.A.: Representative R-NJ (Box 26, Folder 148)
  - Hatfield, Mark: Senator R-OR (Box 26, Folder 149)
  - Hawkes, Albert: Senator R-NJ (Box 26, Folder 150)
  - Hawkins, Augustus: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 151)
  - Hayes, Charles: Representative D-IL (Box 26, Folder 152)
  - Heckler, Margaret M.: Representative R-MA (Box 26, Folder 153)
  - Henning, John: AFL-CIO CA (Box 26, Folder 154)
  - Herman, James: President ILWU (Box 26, Folder 155)
  - Heselton, John: Representative R-MA (Box 26, Folder 156)
  - Hester, Hugh B.: U.S. Army (Box 26, Folder 157)
  - Heusinger, Adolf: U.S. Army General (Box 26, Folder 158)
  - Higgins, James: co-author "Us and Them" (Box 26, Folder 159)
  - Hoff, Philip H.: Governor VT (Box 26, Folder 160)
  - Hoffman, Clare E.: Representative R-MI (Box 26, Folder 161)
  - Holifield, Chet: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 162)
  - Holland, Elmer J.: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 163)
  - Hosmer, Craig: Representative R-CA (Box 26, Folder 164)
  - Howard, Asbury: Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers (Box 26, Folder 165)
  - Hruska, Roman L.: Representative R-NE (Box 26, Folder 166)
  - Hughes, Harold E. Senator D-IA (Box 26, Folder 167)
  - Hughes, Langston: Writer (Box 26, Folder 168)
  - Humphrey, Hubert: Vice President U.S. (Box 26, Folder 169)
  - Hunter, Allan O.: Representative R-CA (Box 26, Folder 170)
  - Ickes, Harold: U.S. Sec of Interior (Box 26, Folder 171)
  - Irwin, Donald J.: Representative D- CT (Box 26, Folder 172)
  - Isacson, Leonard: Representative D-NY (Box 26, Folder 173)
  - Ives, Irving: Senator R-NY (Box 26, Folder 174)
  - Jacob, John: Representative R-OH and Javits, Jacob K. (Box 26, Folder 175)
  - Jennings, Paul: IUE President and Jenkins, Thomas A. (Box 26, Folder 176)
  - Jenner, William E.: Senator R-IN (Box 26, Folder 177)
  - Joelson, Charles S.: Senator D-NJ (Box 26, Folder 178)
  - Johnson, Edwin: Senator D-NJ (Box 26, Folder 179)
  - Johnson, Leroy: Representative R-CA (Box 26, Folder 180)
  - Jones, Rovert: Representative D-OH (Box 26, Folder 181)
  - Judd, Walter H.: Representative R-MN (Box 26, Folder 182)
  - Kastenmeier, Robert W.: Representative D-WI (Box 26, Folder 183)
  - Kean, Frank: Representative R-NJ (Box 26, Folder 184)
  - Kearney, Bernard W. (Pat): Representative R-NY (Box 26, Folder 185)
  - Kearnes, Carroll D.: Representative R-PA (Box 26, Folder 186)
  - Keating, Kenneth B.: Senator R-NY (Box 26, Folder 187)
  - Kennedy, John F.: U.S. President (Box 26, Folder 188)
  - Kennedy, Robert F.: Senator D-NY (Box 26, Folder 189)
  - Kenny, Robert W.: Attorney General CA (Box 26, Folder 190)
  - Kersten, Charles: Representative R-WI (Box 26, Folder 191)
  - Keyserling, Leon: Economist (Box 26, Folder 192)
  - Kilgore, Harley: Senator D-WV (Box 26, Folder 193)
  - King, Cecil R.: Representative D-CA (Box 26, Folder 194)
  - King, Carleton J.: Representative R-NY (Box 26, Folder 195)
  - King, Martin Luther Jr.: Civil Rights Leader (Box 26, Folder 196)
  - Kirwan, Michael: Representative D-OH (Box 26, Folder 197)
  - Klein, Arthur G.: Representative D-NY (Box 26, Folder 198)
  - Klink, Don: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 199)
  - Kluczynski, John C.: Representative D-IL (Box 26, Folder 200)
  - Knoll, Jack: PAC Director for CIO (Box 26, Folder 201)
  - Knowland, William F.: Senator R-CA (Box 26, Folder 202)
  - Knowles, Warren: Governor WI (Box 26, Folder 203)
  - Knutson, Harold: Representative R-MN (Box 26, Folder 204)
  - Koch, Edward I.: Representative D-NY (Box 26, Folder 205)
  - Kolter, Joseph: Representative D-PA (Box 26, Folder 206)
  - Kowalski, Frank: Representative D-CT (Box 26, Folder 207)
  - Kryzcki, Leonard: Labor Leader (Box 26, Folder 208)
  - Kuchel, Thomas H.: Senator R-CA (Box 26, Folder 209)
  - Lafore, John: Representative D-MA (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello: Mayor New York (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Lamont, Corliss: "Prominent American" (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Lane, Thomas J.: Representative D-MA (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Langer, William: Senator R-ND (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Lankford, Richard: Representative D-MD (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Lawson, John Howard: Actor (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Leader, George M.: Senator D-PA (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Leavitt, Marty: Union Busting Attorney (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Lehman, Herbert: Governor NY (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Lesinski, John: Representative D-MI (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Lewis, John L.: Presdient CIO (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Libonati, Roland: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Lincoln, Eric: Professor (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Lindsay, John V.: Mayor NY (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Lipinski, William: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Long, Russell B.: Representative D-LA (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Lucas, Scott: Senator D-IL (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Luscomb, Florence H.: Peace Progressive Candidate for Governor of MA (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Lynch, Frances: UAW President Local 422 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Magdoff, Harry: Economist (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Mahony: Senator (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Malcolm X: Black Civil Rights Leader (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Mansfield, Michael: Senator D-MT (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Marcantino, Vito: Representative D-NY (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Markey, Edward: Representative D-MA (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Marshall, Thurgood: Justice Supreme Court (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Martin, Edward: Senator R-PA (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - May, Edwin H., Jr.: Representative R-CT (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Mazey, Emil: UAW (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Mazzocchi, Anthony: Labor Party Founder (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - McArthur, Douglas: U.S. Military (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - McCarren, Patrick: Senator D-NY (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - McCarthy, Eugene: Senator D-MN (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - McCarthy, Joseph: Senator R-WI (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - McClellan, John L.: Senator D-AR (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - McCloskey, Paul N.: Representative R-CA (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - McConnel, Samuel K.: Representative R-PA (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - McCormack, John W.: Representative D-MA (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - McDonough, Gordon L.: Representative R-CA (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - McDowell, Harris B. Jr.: Representative D-DE (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - McGovern, George: Senator D-SD (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - McNamara, Patrick: Senator D-MI (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Mead, John: Senator D-NY (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Meany, George: President AFL-CIO (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Melman, Seymour: Professor (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Metcalf, Lee: Representative D-MT (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Meyer, William: Representative D-VT (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Miller, Arnold: UMW President (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Mills, Wilbur D.: Senator D-AR (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Mitchell, Edward A.: Representative R-IN (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Mondale, Walter F.: Senator D-MN (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Monroney, Michael: Senator D-OK (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Montgomery, David: Professor (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Moore E.H.: Senator R-OK (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Moorhead, William S.: Representative D-PA (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Morse, Wayne: Senator D-OR (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Mostel, Zero: Actor (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Murray, James: Senator D-MT (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Murray, Philip: Labor Leader (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Muskie, Edmund S.: Senator D-ME (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Neely, Matthew M.: Senator D-WV (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Nelson, Gaylord: Senator D-WI (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: U.S. President (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Norris, George W.: Senator R-NE (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Norton, Mary: Representative D-NJ (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - O'Brien, Thomas J.: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - O'Day, Caroline: Representative D-NY (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - O'Hara, Barratt: Representative D-IL (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - O'Hara, James G.: Representative D-MI (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - O'Neill, Thomas P.: Representative D-MA (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - Owens, Major: Representative D-NY (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - Parren, Mitchell: Representative D-MD (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - Pepper, Claude: Representative D-FL (Box 27, Folder 74)